onpageseotool.com 2014-02-20

# Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

We’ve tried to keep it as simple as possible. Your privacy matters to [onpage seo tool](http://www.onpageseotool.com/) so whether you are new to onpage seo tool or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions consult this page.

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users.

We collect information in one way:

  * **Information we get from your use of our services.** We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you submit an url. This information includes:

    * **Device information**

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers

    * **Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by onpage seo tool, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

      * details of how you used our service.
      * Internet protocol address.
      * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      * cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
    * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a onpage seo tool service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect onpage seo tool and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant urls.

We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. We will not associate a cookie or anonymous identifier with sensitive categories, such as those based on race, religion, sexual orientation or health.

## Information you share

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines, including Google.

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of onpage seo tool unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * **With your consent**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of onpage seo tool when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

  * **For legal reasons**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of onpage seo tool if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * detect, prevent fraud, security or technical issues.
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of onpage seo tool, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by onpage seo tool. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include our services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations.

## Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent.

Last Updated on __Jan 18, 2014
